[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 7]
Tang Tingting!
Lin Zhixia?
What's wrong?
I want to apologize to you.
For what?
We lost
the math contest, because of my arrogance
and mistaken decisions—
I'm so sorry about that.
It's all in the past.
No.
If you hadn't participated
in this contest,
I probably would have failed already
when forming the team.
Then, we made a plan
for intensive training.
But at the last moment,
I ignored my teammates' opinions.
I think my distrust at the time
must have hurt you.
Let me tell you something funny.
What is it?
An underachiever who
got into the experimental class by luck
signed up for the provincial math contest
and aimed for the championship.
During the finals,
she blamed herself for getting
a mandatory question wrong
and almost broke down.
After pulling herself together,
she decided to turn the tide
with a decision
and secure the championship.
After the contest,
she was full of remorse
for only winning runner-up.
With her mother's encouragement
and comfort,
she finally found herself.
She finally remembered—
she was just an underachiever after all.
Lin Zhixia, if it weren't for you,
I wouldn't have
so many inspiring stories to tell.
I just don't know
the next time there's a contest like this,
will Lin Zhixia think of me?
Of course!
Next time,
the time after next,
and the time after that,
we will always be teammates.
Okay!
Let's go.
Listen to this.
My idol's new song.
It's really good.
This medal is really nice.
Look at that engraving.
Tang!
You've been wearing that medal for days.
Aren't you afraid of getting a heat rash?
This heavy medal
is about to bend your small body.
[Constantly Strive to Become Stronger;
Strive to Be Number One]
Achievements
are always heavy.
I'd rather my body be bent a little lower.
The ripe ear of wheat hangs low.
Still annoyed?
It doesn't matter.
There will be a next time.
You don't understand.
It's really very hard this time.
What are you talking about?
Aren't we talking about the contest?
I'm talking about
Han Geng's first concert here.
All that talk—
what you were calling hard was...
It's hard to buy the tickets.
I've prepared the money,
but I can't get a ticket.
My last resort would be going to queue
at 3 AM.
Tang Tingting. Tang Tingting.
You can't just be obsessed...
with chasing celebrities.
Can't you be more like me?
I only care about studying.
Duan Qiyan, let me give you some advice.
Go ahead.
Eighty years from now,
write on your epitaph,
"In the 10th-grade math contest,
I won first prize.
Try doing that too."
That's...
quite a good idea.
Help a sis out.
[Han Geng fans group chat]
Who has tickets?
[I sincerely beg for a ticket.
Willing to add 400 to the base price.]
I sincerely beg for a ticket.
Willing to add 400 to the base price...
[I sincerely beg for a ticket.
Willing to add 800 to the base price.]
800.
[Han Geng fans group chat]
[I didn't get one too.]
[Same here. Also looking to tickets.]
[Cries—I've got no tickets too.]
[Wang Dao 888]
[I know someone.]
The deposit is here.
Angel's Tears!
Did you just
meet another online friend?
What's this online friend's name?
Em0b01?
I'm in a good mood today,
so I won't argue with you.
What's the good news?
I got the tickets!
I'm deaf now, Sis.
No way.
How did you get the tickets?
There's a trick to chasing stars.
Did you see that guy just now?
That was Qian.
Who's that?
Han Geng's cousin.
He's from Mudanjiang.
A real insider.
Didn't you notice his eyes
and his nose
look exactly like Han Geng's?
Han Geng's cousin?
Why would he be in our city?
Every time Han Geng has a concert,
his team would go
in advance for promotion.
And then,
they release some internal tickets
to hardcore fans.
They're all the best seats.
Pay half as a deposit first,
and when you get the ticket at the venue,
you pay the other half.
This way,
it's hundreds cheaper
than a scalper ticket.
This sounds exactly like a scalper.
It's too professional,
you wouldn't understand
even if I explained it.
What a waste of my time.
I got the tickets!
That was Qian.
Han Geng's cousin.
Pay a part of the deposit first,
and when you get the ticket at the venue,
you pay the other half.
It's hundreds cheaper
than a scalper ticket.
This isn't right.
There's definitely something wrong
with that guy.
Mom?
Dad?
[Duan Qiyan is prohibited from using this]
[Han Geng]
[Attention:
girls who are going to the concert.]
[There's been a scammer going around
scamming fans.]
[Han Geng Forum]
[I heard people bought fake tickets.
This person target fans.]
[Someone took a photo of the scammer.]
I can't even...
tell how this person looks like.
[Han Geng scalper tickets]
[Han Geng wanted to do a special concert,]
[yet scalpers drive the prices up.]
[Where is Han Geng from?]
[Does Han Geng have a cousin?]
Jeez!
Sorry.
The number you dialed is out of service.
Sorry...
She has money for a concert
but not for her phone bill.
Seriously...
Ma'am.
Is Tingting home?
She went to her grandmother's house.
Said she wanted to eat
her grandmother's cooking.
To her grandmother's house?
Duan.
Why are you looking for Tingting?
Nothing, Ma'am.
I was going to ask her a math question.
If she's not here, never mind.
I'll get going.
Bye-bye.
Are you sure Tang Tingting got scammed?
Of course.
Although I'm not 100% sure,
my intuition tells me
there's definitely something wrong
with that guy.
Why?
Paying a deposit
before getting the ticket—
it's most likely a scam.
Besides,
I found a very important piece
of evidence!
Han Geng doesn't have a cousin!
Tang Tingting told me
that the scalper is Han Geng's cousin.
So I went online
and searched for a whole morning.
But Han Geng doesn't have a cousin!
You searched online for the whole morning?
All morning.
No matter what,
we have to find him.
What if something bad happens?
But how do we find her?
We don't even know
where she went to get the ticket.
I have a idea.
But I need your help.
[No use of Duan Qiyan]
Let's do this.
Don't panic.
Let's do this one by one.
Actually, this is very simple.
Since we can't find Tang Tingting,
we go directly to Qian.
The local fan group chat must have clues.
We can just sneak in
and take a look.
[Would you like to join "Geng Babes"
as "Death Scythe"?]
[The moderator
has rejected your application.]
Heh...
Local fan group chats like this
usually only admit hardcore fans.
With a profile picture of Kobe
and a username like "Death Scythe,"
you're obviously not a fan.
Let me do it.
[Personal information:
One & Only Geng]
This is good.
[The moderator
has approved your application.]
You're in!
That's amazing, Shen.
[Geng Babes]
[Genggeng Forever
invites you to "Geng Babes'" voice call]
[Please answer the voice call.
I'll give you the test right now.]
Please answer the voice call.
I'll give you the test right now.
Here.
Voice test?
Hello?
I'm a moderator, Genggeng Forever.
We will now test you
for the group chat admission.
What is Han Geng's debut date?
Do you know?
[Please answer the voice call.
I'll give you the test right now.]
[You've been kicked out
of the group chat by the moderator.]
Well, Shen,
you're not a fan either.
Duan Qiyan, you type fast.
I'll take the call later.
You just search for the answer online.
Okay.
[Geng Babes]
[Genggeng Forever]
Hello.
I'm Hearts4Geng.
We will now conduct
the group admission test.
[One & Only Geng] [Genggeng Forever]
What is Han Geng's fan song?
[Han Geng's fan song]
"Wings of Love."
Very good.
Which year
did Han Geng have a hellish schedule?
[Han Geng hellish schedule]
2009.
Okay, the last question.
Please listen carefully.
[One & Only Geng] [Genggeng Forever]
Please name this song.
I...
[One & Only Geng] [Genggeng Forever]
Do you know?
I don't.
[One & Only Geng] [Genggeng Forever]
[Please answer the voice call.
I'll give you the test right now.]
[You've been kicked out
of the group chat by the moderator.]
What should we do?
Han Geng has over a dozen songs so far.
Who could figure out the song
just by listening to it for a few seconds?
Memorizing the intros
to over a dozen songs in a short time
is an impossible task for someone like me
who can't sing.
But memorizing images
is a piece of cake to me.
I can give this method a try.
[Han Geng-"The Moth Rushes Toward Fire"]
"The Moth Rushes Toward Fire."
That's correct.
[Baby Genggeng] [Genggeng Forever]
"Separated."
That's correct.
The last song.
[Baby Genggeng] [Genggeng Forever]
"Life is But a Dream."
That's correct.
Welcome to the Geng Babes family.
[Baby Genggeng] [Genggeng Forever]
Does anyone know Qian?
[Welcome to the Geng Babes family.]
Tell them you want to buy tickets too.
Yes, say you're looking for a ticket.
[Does anyone know Qian?]
I'm looking for a ticket.
[I'm looking for a ticket.]
Let's see how he replies.
He's distributing tickets
at the small gate on the west side
of the venue at 4:30 PM today.
-Got it.
Let's go. What are you waiting for?
Go!
-Let's go.
Jiang Yubai.
Do you want to switch seats?
Isn't it too crowded for you 3 guys?
Sure—
Nope.
I-I-I really like sitting in the middle.
The middle has a wide view—it's great.
And it feels snug.
Very comfortable.
What?
It feels snug.
Is that so?
Yeah.
It's a bit too squeezy
on my side right now.
That's too snug.
That's too much.
Shen!
Stop squeezing.
L-Let's set off.
Let's go.
Duan Qiyan, wait up!
Tang.
Sorry.
Tang! Tang!
Sorry, I got the wrong person.
Duan Qiyan, why are you here?
Your phone is out of credit.
Couldn't you have topped it up?
Really?
What were you calling me for?
Something's up, obviously.
Duan Qiyan, why did you run off so quickly?
Why are you all here?
You got the ticket?
But... But where's that scammer?
The guy who you met yesterday?
I'll tell you again.
He's not a swindler. He's Qian.
He was just here.
He gave me the ticket.
Can I have a look?
First row?
Is this Qian really that amazing?
[Beyond the Prologue 2010]
[World Tour—Nanhai Stop]
[Beyond the Prologue World Tour—Nanhai Stop]
Wait.
The English word for "Stadium"—
it's typed as "Stadiam."
Would official tickets
make this kind of mistake?
Impossible.
Scan it again.
My ticket can't be fake.
Young girl, your ticket is obviously fake.
Real tickets have official watermarks
and holo marks.
Plus, in this section,
there is no such seat number.
Are you sure you bought it
through an official platform?
I bought it from a friend.
He's Han Geng's cousin.
He promised it was real.
Cousin?
Yeah right, Han Geng's cousin.
Duan Qiyan!
Stop talking.
Didn't I tell you?
That guy was obviously a scammer.
Tang Tingting, how old are you?
You keep falling for this,
over and over again.
Look around now.
There is not a single soul here.
Where are you going to catch him?
He ran away long ago.
Can you just shut up?
I saved up for half a year just for this.
Mind your own business.
So what if I got scammed?
Hey...
Don't cry.
I was wrong, okay?
I'm just worried about you
and am doing this for your own good.
All right, as long as you're okay.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
I'll just consider it
a lesson learned with money.
No.
You didn't do anything wrong.
Why should you pay to learn a lesson?
Tang Tingting.
Give me Qian's phone number.
Hello?
Who is it?
Hello, is this Qian?
Do you still have concert tickets?
Yes.
I need them urgently.
I'll pay whatever extra you want.
How many do you need?
How many?
Two. Including me.
I'm her boyfriend.
Sure.
But it's about to start.
You have to pay extra.
880 a ticket.
Plus the fee for adjacent seats.
That'd be 2,200.
Sure, no problem.
Where should we meet?
The milk tea shop
on the west street of the stadium.
You know it, right?
Let's meet there.
In 20 minutes.
I'll wait for you on the 1st floor.
Be quick.
There won't be tickets left
if you're late.
Okay, we'll be right there.
Jiang Yubai.
Why did you suddenly
add a role for yourself?
Are you comfortable
letting Lin Zhixia go alone?
Let's go. We only have 20 minutes.
Who brought money?
Zhixia, who goes out with 2,200?
Just in case.
I happen to have brought money.
Are you Qian?
I would like the tickets.
Who is this handsome guy?
I'm her boyfriend.
Did you bring the money?
You're too late.
The ticket check is about to start.
Here, hurry up.
Aren't you going to check the amount?
No need. Your show is about to start.
Hurry up. Don't waste time.
Hold on.
Count the money carefully before leaving.
Fine, I'll count it.
Let me count it.
All right. Let me see.
Are you okay?
Trying to run, huh?
I won't run!
I won't run. I won't run.
Ouch, ouch.
The police are here!
The police are here.
Officer!
It's him. He's selling fake tickets.
Officer, this is nonsense.
Tell me—
where do I even have a single ticket?
I don't have any tickets on me.
On what basis do you say
I'm selling fake tickets?
Stop lying.
You're the head fan
they mentioned on the forum.
It's him.
He swore he would have tickets.
But he just scammed me.
Listen, miss.
In this internet age,
you can't even tell
if you're talking to a person
or a machine online.
Why do you say it was me?
Do you have proof?
If you didn't sell us fake tickets,
then why do you have our money?
This is even more ridiculous.
She's saying
that my money is hers.
What?
If you call out to it,
will it answer you?
I can.
RE72591436.
RT68604243.
QM59284713.
To prove that Qian is indeed suspicious,
we had to memorize
the serial numbers on these bills.
You memorized all of them
in such a short time?
Don't we have phones?
We just took pictures.
CT12377756.
AB74255931.
EM08351742.
XY14709265.
All correct.
Didn't you just glance at them
when taking the pictures?
And I just memorized them then.
To prevent getting scammed,
we specifically memorized them
before buying the tickets.
Of course, we will need the officers
to verify who they belong to.
But once it's verified
that the money is indeed ours,
even if you don't admit
to selling us fake tickets,
you'll still have to explain
why our money is with you.
If you can't explain it...
We can reasonably suspect
that you committed theft.
Hey.
Fraud or theft—
pick one.
They...
Bro.
You thought hiding would keep you safe,
but you didn't expect us
to have the smartest brain.
Doing a good deed a day
will keep the moonlight bright at night.
Tang,
I didn't expect you to do a good deed.
The police said
that he is an experienced scammer.
He's not one to admit
to selling fake tickets.
This is thanks to you, Zhixia.
How did you think of that?
I just felt
that the reason he used cash
must be because
he was afraid of being traced.
Since when making the deal,
he had no witnesses or evidence,
we'd have to create witnesses
and evidence for him.
Anyway, our money is with him.
He has to admit to either theft or fraud.
We're also lucky today.
If the scalper wasn't greedy,
he wouldn't have come back.
Right.
Fortunately,
apart from missing the concert,
we didn't lose anything.
I just want to see a concert.
What use do I have for the money?
And Han Geng is here only for one concert
this year.
Why is it so hard to watch a concert?
If you want to watch the concert,
it's not impossible.
When we walked over just now,
I noticed that
the acoustics
in each area are a bit different.
Looking at the structure of this venue,
there must be a place
with the best acoustics.
Let's go find it.
That was my first time at a concert.
Even though before today,
I didn't even know who was singing inside.
But now, as soon as I hear the intro,
I know the name of the song.
I know the propagation characteristics
of high-frequency
and low-frequency sound waves.
I also took Tang Tingting and the others
to find the spot outside
with the best acoustics.
There were people waving light sticks,
instantly lighting up a sea of lights.
We hummed songs out of tune
and danced stiffly.
I can't remember
the muffled singing inside,
but my memory of the concert
is paused at the starry sky
we lit up for ourselves
with flashlights and out-of-tune voices.
Our Han Geng is so handsome.
Did you see Han Geng in person today?
Mind your own business.
Han Geng is just handsome.
The most handsome.
Right, Duan Qiyan?
Yes, Han Geng is handsome.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking about
how I gained a new experience today.
It's my first time at a concert,
and it was with you too.
I realize a lot of my firsts
are with you.
My first time having a deskmate.
My first time
receiving a birthday present.
My first time going to an aquarium.
Then,
is there anything else you want to do?
I hope that
when I go to Mars for the first time,
you can be by my side too.
Do you want some?
No, I'm too full.
Shen.
Shen!
Do you want some?
Thanks.
I want to go... to the National Museum,
the Louvre,
an amusement park,
a water park—
This can be done.
Let's go to the amusement park tomorrow.
Sure!
Amusement park? Sounds good.
-Hey, I'm not...
-Didn't you ask
if we want to go
to the amusement park tomorrow?
I meant...
Hey, Duan Qiyan, Tang Tingting.
Jiang Yubai is asking if we want to go
to the amusement park tomorrow.
-Sure!
Tell you what,
it's my treat. To thank you guys.
Sure!
[Fantasy Kingdom]
Friends, let's be the first ones in!
I'm so sleepy.
We have a really intense schedule
this weekend.
I made a plan last night.
We must complete
every single ride today.
Thank you, Tang Tingting.
My parents are busy with work,
so they never brought me here.
It's no big deal.
Of course you come to an amusement park
with friends.
Let's go.
[Fantasy Kingdom]
Hello!
Are you students?
Yes.
Our amusement park
recently launched a new event.
[Mission Box]
It's called the Mission Card event.
Would you like to have a try?
What is it about?
Here's how it works:
when you enter the park later,
[Mission Box]
everyone will wear
a badge like this on their chest.
[Mission Box]
Then from my box,
you'll draw your hidden missions.
You have to complete this mission
avoiding getting caught by others.
Once someone successfully calls you out,
your mission fails,
and this badge will go to them.
When you leave the park,
whoever has the most badges
[Mission Box]
will be the winner.
That sounds quite interesting.
Yeah.
We have a lot of people, so it's perfect.
I don't think
anyone likes losing in our class.
I might not beat you in exams,
but I'm pretty good at playing games.
You've successfully ignited
my competitive spirit.
Bring it on!
Let's do it.
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
[Touch each player's hand once]
For every player, each of you
only has one chance to call them out.
If you are not sure,
please don't use it casually.
Enjoy!
Thanks!
Let's go.
Okay.
Princess.
Her Royal Highness the Princess
has arrived.
Look at this.
How about adding a little flower?
This smell is not right.
It can also block the sun.
Wearing this...
Looks so funny on you.
What is that?
A flower fairy.
Here.
Did you draw the mission
where you have to
hide the weird-flavored candy on everyone?
Hurry up. Let me pay.
[Tang Tingting's Mission]
[Hide the weird-flavored candy
on everyone]
[without being discovered.]
Tingting!
Which one do you want?
Anything is fine.
This one.
I think this one suits you.
Sure. I'll take this one, then.
How much is it?
First, get out of this castle.
And then
let's go to the "Flooded Jinshan" ride.
It's like a giant swing.
Is it that scary?
You'll find out soon.
There's a momentary feeling
of weightlessness on the pirate ship.
Weightlessness?
Sometimes when I dream,
I wake up startled from falling.
Would you be scared?
Probably not.
Every time I come to the amusement park,
I imagine it as an astronaut test,
so I won't be scared.
Next group of visitors.
Be careful and head inside.
I suddenly don't feel so good.
You guys go ahead.
You can give me your stuff.
I'll watch it for you.
Sure.
Can you hold this for me too?
Hurry up.
The ride is about to start.
You guys wait for the next round.
What are you doing?
I... I bought candy for everyone.
I'm passing it out.
Are you trying to complete a mission?
No way.
Tang, you're being too obvious.
Before we came, you said
you wanted to go on all the rides here.
This is only the first one.
Please.
Let me off this time.
It's embarrassing
to be the first one caught.
Nope!
Your mission is...
Are you sure you want to say it?
Everyone only has one chance.
If you guess wrong,
you'll waste your chance.
To sneak everyone candy
without being discovered.
[Tang Tingting's mission:
hide the weird-flavored candy
on everyone]
[without being discovered.]
[Fail]
This is mine now.
Give it to me.
You're no fun.
Was it fun?
It was fun.
I actually like
the feeling of weightlessness.
Then you have the potential
to be an astronaut.
Shen Fuxuan is the impressive one.
He didn't make a sound the whole time.
Are you not scared
because you go on rides often,
or because you're brave?
[Shen Fuxuan's Mission]
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
I'm brave.
[Shen Fuxuan's Mission]
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
[Shen Fuxuan: 2 sentences left]
Here.
No wonder you suddenly said
you were not playing earlier.
So this is why.
What's her mission?
To slip candy into everyone's pockets
without being noticed.
But I caught her on the first try.
It's just a side quest.
Why so serious?
You still need to be competitive.
Stop showing off.
I don't even care about this stupid badge.
I just feel relieved now, okay?
Sure, sure.
Let's go.
Next stop, roller coaster.
Shen.
Well, are you scared?
I heard this thing
always malfunctions overseas.
I don't know if it's safe.
He's too scared to ride.
I'm talking to you.
Why are you ignoring me?
You don't have to ride it
if you're scared.
No one is forcing you.
Acrophobia is half hereditary.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
Seems like you didn't take the pirate ship
cause you were scared.
You just happened
to catch me sneaking candy.
Nonsense.
I'm just a little excited
before getting on.
Also, I'm just communicating with Shen.
Right?
[Please queue in twos]
It must be fun.
Duan Qiyan.
Even though
I've never ridden a roller coaster,
from my observation,
the back row should be the scariest.
Th-The scariest?
When the front row starts to dive,
the back row is still climbing,
converting accumulated potential energy
into stronger acceleration.
Wait.
But—
You want to take this seat, right?
Let's switch, then!
Have my seat.
Go ahead.
Sir, could we switch seats?
Sure.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
You obviously
can't handle high-altitude rides.
Why force yourself?
Guess you can't be an astronaut.
Was your mission
to ride the roller coaster?
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have dared to get on.
It really isn't.
You guessed wrong.
You have no more chances left.
[Shen Fuxuan's Mission]
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
[Shen Fuxuan: 1 sentence left]
I got it. Your mission is...
Ms. Xia!
No rush.
There's still a long time left
in this game.
Take your time to guess.
If you guess wrong, you lose your chance.
Your mission is to make
a peace sign on the roller coaster.
You got it.
Hand it over.
Hand it over!
Stop!
-You lost.
-Slow down!
Watch my...
Why did you pinch me?
You finally get what you deserve.
Two.
Not bad, Shen.
I guess it's not 100%,
but...
you're not bad.
I have one question.
Just now when we were playing bumper cars,
why did you guys keep crashing into me?
-We didn't.
Yes, you did.
My back is all red.
So fragile.
Shen Fuxuan.
Help get everyone their ice cream cones.
Sure.
[Shen Fuxuan's Mission]
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
[Shen Fuxuan: 0 sentences left]
You kept blocking my way.
So I had to crash into you.
I was just...
Thanks.
What about mine, Jiang?
Over there.
My back still hurts from the crash.
Hello. Can you come over here for a sec?
Sure.
What's going on?
Hello.
I feel a connection with you.
Although not as much
as with the guy opposite you,
the athletic high schooler...
You're making that up, aren't you?
I want to be friends with you.
Can I get your contact info?
He gave it.
Jiang is very charming.
Wow, for real?
Let's ride the drop tower.
Sure, let's go!
Let's go!
Come on, we've rested enough. Let's go.
Go.
Where to?
The drop tower.
Jiang.
The gentle senior type like you
is really attractive to girls.
What are you talking about?
What is that?
Don't you think so, Shen Fuxuan?
Why are you acting so weird today?
You haven't said a word.
Did I offend you?
Wait a minute.
Are you doing the side mission?
I got it.
Your mission is to not speak for a day.
He did speak.
Did he?
Let me think...
[Exit]
Are you not scared
because you go on rides often,
or because you're brave?
I'm brave.
[Shen Fuxuan's 1st sentence]
Is your task to ride the roller coaster?
Otherwise, you definitely wouldn't get on.
[Shen Fuxuan's 2nd sentence]
Shen Fuxuan.
Help get everyone their ice cream cones.
Sure.
[Shen Fuxuan's 3rd sentence]
Is your task
not to speak more than 3 sentences a day?
[Shen Fuxuan's Mission]
[You can't talk more than 3 sentences
during the game.]
[Fail]
Good memory.
Hand it over.
Thanks.
Let's go.
We're here!
Wow, that's so high.
I... I need the toilet.
Are you too scared to ride?
How is that possible?
I just ate
too much ice cream just now.
My stomach is a bit upset.
I'll be right back.
He's just scared.
He's been a coward since childhood.
You guys go first.
I must drag him up here today.
I'll help you.
Then how about
the two of us ride first?
Jiang Yubai, you're really popular.
Even a passerby
wants to exchange numbers with you.
I feel like you can make friends
wherever you go.
Actually... I didn't give her my number.
I just feel
it's quite awkward
to reject someone in public.
So I left her
our school's number.
But actually, it's fine
if you left your own number.
I read in a book before:
most friends
can only accompany you
for a part of your life's journey.
When they reach their destination,
they will get off,
and watch you go to the next stop.
You will definitely have
even more friends in the future.
I hope by then,
I can still be your best friend—
one of them.
It stopped.
I-It's so high.
Are you scared?
No.
Actually, a little bit.
Do you have any unfulfilled wishes?
That sounds like an unlucky thing
to be talking about now.
I'm a bit nervous.
I want to distract myself.
All right, then.
Go ahead.
I'll chat with you.
Do you have any other secrets?
I don't think so.
What about you?
I...
Does being about to fall asleep
in a second count?
How does that count?
By the way,
though you just said
that all friends last just for a phase,
I want to say...
I want to
be with you forever.
You will always be my one and only...
best friend.
So this is what it feels like
to ride a drop tower.
When we were up there just now,
for a moment,
I thought we'd never come down.
I saw you were scared, so I...
I'm glad you were by my side.
Duan Qiyan, it's a good thing
you didn't go on the drop tower.
Otherwise, you would've cried.
Is it that scary?
No point telling you.
You didn't even dare to ride it.
Why bother asking?
Cut the crap.
You've been moping all day
and haven't said a word.
You really held it in
just for a side quest.
Cut the crap.
I didn't want to talk today anyway.
Sure.
Keep telling yourself that.
This quest would've killed you
in 10 minutes.
I'm not as competitive as you are!
You guys are out.
How was it today?
Did you have fun?
It was fun, just a bit tiring.
Seems like today's winner
is this lady.
No, no.
I didn't finish my mission,
so it shouldn't count.
What's your mission?
To exchange something with each of you.
But I couldn't find a chance
with Jiang Yubai.
I think this suits you well.
That works. Let's go with this then.
My headband.
Shen Fuxuan,
my gun doesn't seem to work well.
Can we swap?
The gun?
Wait.
What did we exchange?
Roller coaster seats.
You want to take this seat, right?
Let's switch, then!
That's too subtle.
Who would notice that?
Actually,
you exchanged something with me too.
On the drop tower,
didn't we exchange secrets?
You will always be my one and only...
best friend.
Jiang.
You're even helping
your opponent make up for it.
Looks like Lin Zhixia
is 1st place again today,
and I'm Ms. Last Place again.
Isn't that normal?
So what's your mission?
Me?
Hand it over!
[Jiang Yubai's Mission]
[Touch each player's hand once]
[Duan Qiyan]
[Tang Tingting]
[Touch each player's hand once]
[Shen Fuxuan]
I didn't finish my mission either.
[Jiang Yubai's Mission]
[Touch each player's hand once]
[Lin Zhixia]
What is it?
To tell a joke to everyone.
A joke?
You really weren't
participating in this game at all.
It makes me look stupid.
That's so boring of you.
This isn't like you.
I didn't perform well.
Do you guys want to take a group photo?
I'll give it to you for free.
Sure!
Let's go. Come this way.
Okay!
Can't say no to free.
Find your spots.
Strike a pose.
Three, two, one.
I suddenly wish
time could freeze at this moment.
Not because it is so perfect,
but so that when my future self
looks at this photo on some evening,
I can still hear the laughter
of this moment
and feel the warmth
of someone staying close to me.
The years are long.
It is these shining fragments
captured by the camera
that illuminate the highlights
of our lives.
Why aren't you asleep yet?
Explain yourself.
Curfew is at 9 PM.
What time is it now?
I had things to do today.
I already told Mom and Dad.
Is that a reason?
Yes.
Don't let it happen again.
Are you waiting for me?
No.
I'm admiring the moon.
Keep admiring then.
[Certificate of Honor]
[Tang Tingting won the 2nd place]
[in the Star of Hope Math Contest]
[Xuan,
I'm going to an academic conference.]
[Take good care of yourself this week.]
[Xuan,
I'm going to an academic conference.]
[Take good care of yourself this week.]
[Mission Card]
[Touch each player's hand once]
I want to tell you,
I want to be with you forever.
[Mission Card]
[Touch each player's hand once]